widerfunnel.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Statement - WiderFunnel Conversion Optimization

**Last updated: June 15, 2018**

**WiderFunnel Marketing Inc.** (from here on out, WiderFunnel) recognizes that protecting personal information is vitally important. We are committed to ensuring that we comply with British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act (“PIPA”) and other applicable legislation. We also look to international best practices when it comes to protecting the personal information that we collect, use and disclose during the course of business.

This Privacy Statement is designed to provide transparency regarding our privacy practices. Please read it to ensure you understand how we handle the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. If you don’t want us to use your personal information in the ways identified here, you should not use our website or services (referred to together from now on as our “Services”).

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Statement, please contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@widerfunnel.com](mailto:privacy@widerfunnel.com).  

WiderFunnel may collect personal information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or email address, through the Registration Information forms.We may also collect certain information from website visitors, such as Internet address, user IDs and passwords and contact preferences. Where this information can be used to identify you personally, we will treat it as personal information.

### Disclosure

WiderFunnel will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose personal information to any third parties or outside companies for any reasons other than those specified below unless we obtain your consent to do so.

Where requests for information about our Services come from outside North America, we may share your personal information with third parties. For example, WiderFunnel does not offer goods and services in the EU. Where requests come from the EU, we will forward personal information (name, email address, phone number) to our global partners who can provide full-service marketing experimentation consulting. Please see [Global Optimization Group](https://www.globaloptimizationgroup.com/) site for more information.

If you are requesting information from outside North America, you understand and consent to WiderFunnel disclosing your personal information to our global partners.  
WiderFunnel may also disclose personal information to comply with any laws, regulations, court orders, subpoenas, or other legal process or investigation and to protect ourselves and other individuals from harm.

We may disclose your information to other third parties in relation to a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all our assets or business. Your information may be provided to the entities and advisors involved, for the purposes of determining whether to proceed with the transaction and, where applicable, to conclude the transaction. Your information may be transferred to a successor or assign of all or part of our assets or business that may use and disclose the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement.

### Use of information

WiderFunnel uses contact information, including email addresses and phone numbers, to:

  * To respond to your requests for information.
  * To establish customer accounts.
  * To contact you with updates, newsletters and notifications regarding our Services, where we have your consent to do so.

We may also collect “de-identified data”, data that does not identify an individual, including demographic data. We use this de-identified data to:

  * Gather information on general interest in products and analyze product usage, purchasing and target markets.
  * Monitor system usage, server and software performance, to improve system design, to create benchmarks and to conduct trend analyses.
  * Perform statistical analyses and generate data related to how you use our website.

We may use this de-identified data internally or share it with our partners, for example, service providers, but the information will not identify you specifically. For example, we may share it in aggregate form for marketing and other promotional purposes.

### Consent

WiderFunnel will obtain your consent prior to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We do not require you to provide us with personal information, the decision to do so it is voluntary. If you do not wish to provide personal information, we may not be able to provide you with Services and you may not receive the benefits associated with providing personal information.

At any time and without penalty, you can withdraw your consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Statement by contacting us at [privacy@widerfunnel.com](mailto:privacy@widerfunnel.com) or, in the case of marketing emails, by clicking on the unsubscribe link found in each email message.

### Retaining Personal Information

We will retain personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or as permitted or required by law. Contact information that you provide to us for communications purposes will be retained until you unsubscribe or request to be removed from our database.

We do not retain your personal information when we forward contact requests to global partners.

### Security of data

We maintain appropriate processing practices and security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification or disposal or destruction. We train our team to follow privacy and security practices and use contracts to ensure that third parties acting on our behalf also maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards.

Even so, it is important to remember that the Internet is not an absolutely secure medium of communication and no system can be guaranteed 100% secure, not even WiderFunnel’s.

### Cookies

We use functional cookies on our website to deliver the desired functionality and user experience, analytics cookies to collect and analyze aggregate visitor behavior data in an effort to improve our website. Finally, we use marketing cookies to grow our audience and reach previous visitors with new content.

For more information about cookies and to opt-out from our cookies, please go to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.widerfunnel.com/cookie-policy/).

### Remarketing

We use Google AdWords, Facebook, LinkedIn and Quora remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. This allows us to provide targeted advertising about our services and content in the future. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

To learn more about remarketing use of cookies, please check our [Cookie Policy](https://www.widerfunnel.com/cookie-policy/).

### Third-party sites

WiderFunnel website may link to other sites as a convenience to users. This Privacy Statement does not govern those other sites and we are not responsible for their privacy practices or website contents. While we do our best to research and link to the most trustworthy sites that we visit ourselves, you should read their privacy statements and make an informed decision about whether you want to use those websites or their services or provide them with your personal information.

### Location of Services

WiderFunnel processes and stores data in the U.S. and Canada.

### Access to and accuracy of your information

It is your responsibility to ensure that information you provide to WiderFunnel is accurate. You may request access to, make corrections to, or delete the personal information we hold about you at any time, subject to limited exceptions.

Upon written request, we will provide you with a list of entities (e.g. affiliate partners and third party service providers) to whom we have disclosed your personal information, if applicable.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

WiderFunnel may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. We will post the date of the most recent changes and provide previous versions upon request. If we make significant changes, we will provide a more prominent notice (including email notification if appropriate).

### Questions or comments

You may send your privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints to our Privacy Officer, who is responsible for ensuring our compliance with this statement and privacy legislation.

Privacy Officer  
Suite 1480, 333 Seymour Street  
Vancouver, BC V6B 5A6  
Canada  
Email: [privacy@widerfunnel.com](mailto:privacy@widerfunnel.com)

If our Privacy Officer is unable to resolve the concern, you may also write to the [Information and Privacy Commissioner of British Columbia](https://www.oipc.bc.ca/).
